<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>InfoMark</title>
    <link>https://infomark.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on InfoMark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infomark.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark/</guid>
      <description> infomark A CI based course framework
Synopsis InfoMark is a a scalable, modern and open-source online course management system supporting auto-testing/grading of programming assignments and distributing exercise sheets. The infomark-server is the REST api backend for the course distributing system.
Complete documentation is available at https://infomark.org/.
Options -h, --help help for infomark SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark serve - start the infomark RESTful JSON backend server with configured api infomark work - start a worker  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console/</guid>
      <description>infomark console infomark console commands
Synopsis infomark console commands
Options -h, --help help for console SEE ALSO  infomark - A CI based course framework infomark console admin - Management of global admins. infomark console configuration - infomark configuration commands infomark console course - Management of cours assignment infomark console database - Management of database. infomark console group - Management of groups infomark console submission - Management of submission infomark console user - Management of users infomark console utils - Some helper functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin/</guid>
      <description> infomark console admin Management of global admins.
Synopsis Management of global admins.
Options -h, --help help for admin SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console admin add - set gives an user global admin permission infomark console admin remove - removes global admin permission from a user  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin_add/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin_add/</guid>
      <description> infomark console admin add set gives an user global admin permission
Synopsis Will set the gobal root flag to &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; for a given user bypassing all permission tests
infomark console admin add [userID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for add SEE ALSO  infomark console admin - Management of global admins.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin_remove/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_admin_remove/</guid>
      <description> infomark console admin remove removes global admin permission from a user
Synopsis Will set the gobal root flag to false for a user
infomark console admin remove [userID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for remove SEE ALSO  infomark console admin - Management of global admins.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration/</guid>
      <description> infomark console configuration infomark configuration commands
Synopsis infomark configuration commands
Options -h, --help help for configuration SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console configuration create - will create and print a configuration to stdout infomark console configuration create-compose - create docker-compose file from config infomark console configuration test - will create and print a configuration to stdout  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_create-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_create-compose/</guid>
      <description> infomark console configuration create-compose create docker-compose file from config
Synopsis create docker-compose file from config
infomark console configuration create-compose [configfile] [flags] Options -h, --help help for create-compose SEE ALSO  infomark console configuration - infomark configuration commands  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_create/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_create/</guid>
      <description> infomark console configuration create will create and print a configuration to stdout
Synopsis will create and print a configuration to stdout
infomark console configuration create [flags] Options -h, --help help for create SEE ALSO  infomark console configuration - infomark configuration commands  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_configuration_test/</guid>
      <description> infomark console configuration test will create and print a configuration to stdout
Synopsis will create and print a configuration to stdout
infomark console configuration test [configfile] [flags] Options -h, --help help for test -t, --test string Test target for configuration (default &amp;#34;server&amp;#34;) SEE ALSO  infomark console configuration - infomark configuration commands  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_course/</guid>
      <description> infomark console course Management of cours assignment
Synopsis Management of cours assignment
Options -h, --help help for course SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console course enroll - will enroll a user into course  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_course_enroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_course_enroll/</guid>
      <description> infomark console course enroll will enroll a user into course
Synopsis will enroll a user into course
infomark console course enroll [courseID] [userID] [role] [flags] Options -h, --help help for enroll SEE ALSO  infomark console course - Management of cours assignment  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database/</guid>
      <description> infomark console database Management of database.
Synopsis Management of database.
Options -h, --help help for database SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console database backup - backup database to a file infomark console database migrate - migrate database to latest version infomark console database restore - restore database from a file infomark console database run - run a sql command  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_backup/</guid>
      <description> infomark console database backup backup database to a file
Synopsis Will dump the entire database to a snapshot file
infomark console database backup [file.sql.gz] [flags] Options -h, --help help for backup SEE ALSO  infomark console database - Management of database.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_migrate/</guid>
      <description> infomark console database migrate migrate database to latest version
Synopsis manually run database migration
infomark console database migrate [flags] Options -h, --help help for migrate SEE ALSO  infomark console database - Management of database.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_restore/</guid>
      <description> infomark console database restore restore database from a file
Synopsis Will clean entire database and load a snapshot
infomark console database restore [file.sql.gz] [flags] Options -h, --help help for restore SEE ALSO  infomark console database - Management of database.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_database_run/</guid>
      <description> infomark console database run run a sql command
Synopsis run a SQl statement. This statement will persistently changes entries!
infomark console database run [sql] [flags] Options -h, --help help for run SEE ALSO  infomark console database - Management of database.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group Management of groups
Synopsis Management of groups
Options -h, --help help for group SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console group bids - list all bids of a user infomark console group dump-bids - export group-bids of all users in a course infomark console group enroll - enroll a student to a group infomark console group import-assignments - parse solution and assign students to groups infomark console group list - list all groups from a specific course infomark console group locate - locate a student in a group  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_bids/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group bids list all bids of a user
Synopsis list all bids of a user
infomark console group bids [courseID] [userID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for bids SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_dump-bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_dump-bids/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group dump-bids export group-bids of all users in a course
Synopsis for assignment
infomark console group dump-bids [courseID] [file] [min_per_group] [max_per_group] [flags] Options -h, --help help for dump-bids SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_enroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_enroll/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group enroll enroll a student to a group
Synopsis enroll a student to a group or update enrollment if student is already enrolled in another group
infomark console group enroll [groupID] [userID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for enroll SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_import-assignments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_import-assignments/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group import-assignments parse solution and assign students to groups
Synopsis for assignment
infomark console group import-assignments [courseID] [file] [flags] Options -h, --help help for import-assignments SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_list/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group list list all groups from a specific course
Synopsis shows information about exercise groups with their description and number of assigned students
infomark console group list [courseID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for list SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_locate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_group_locate/</guid>
      <description> infomark console group locate locate a student in a group
Synopsis show the exercise group for a given student
infomark console group locate [courseID] [userID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for locate SEE ALSO  infomark console group - Management of groups  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission/</guid>
      <description> infomark console submission Management of submission
Synopsis Management of submission
Options -h, --help help for submission SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console submission run - run tests for a submission without writing to db infomark console submission trigger - put submission into testing queue infomark console submission trigger_all - trigger_all tests all submissions for a given task  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_run/</guid>
      <description> infomark console submission run run tests for a submission without writing to db
Synopsis will enqueue a submission again into the testing queue
infomark console submission run [submissionID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for run SEE ALSO  infomark console submission - Management of submission  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_trigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_trigger/</guid>
      <description> infomark console submission trigger put submission into testing queue
Synopsis will enqueue a submission again into the testing queue
infomark console submission trigger [submissionID] [flags] Options -h, --help help for trigger SEE ALSO  infomark console submission - Management of submission  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_trigger_all/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_submission_trigger_all/</guid>
      <description> infomark console submission trigger_all trigger_all tests all submissions for a given task
Synopsis Will enqueue all submissions for a given task again into the testing queue This triggers all [kind]-tests again (private, public).
infomark console submission trigger_all [taskID] [kind] [flags] Options -h, --help help for trigger_all SEE ALSO  infomark console submission - Management of submission  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user/</guid>
      <description> infomark console user Management of users
Synopsis Management of users
Options -h, --help help for user SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console user confirm - confirms the email address manually infomark console user find - find user by first_name, last_name or email infomark console user set-email - will alter the email address  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_confirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_confirm/</guid>
      <description> infomark console user confirm confirms the email address manually
Synopsis Will run confirmation procedure for an user
infomark console user confirm [email] [flags] Options -h, --help help for confirm SEE ALSO  infomark console user - Management of users  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_find/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_find/</guid>
      <description> infomark console user find find user by first_name, last_name or email
Synopsis List all users matching the query
infomark console user find [query] [flags] Options -h, --help help for find SEE ALSO  infomark console user - Management of users  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_set-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_user_set-email/</guid>
      <description> infomark console user set-email will alter the email address
Synopsis Will change email address of an user without confirmation procedure
infomark console user set-email [userID] [email] [flags] Options -h, --help help for set-email SEE ALSO  infomark console user - Management of users  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils/</guid>
      <description> infomark console utils Some helper functions.
Synopsis Some helper functions.
Options -h, --help help for utils SEE ALSO  infomark console - infomark console commands infomark console utils completion - Output (bash/zsh) shell completion code infomark console utils doc - Generates docs for console  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils_completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils_completion/</guid>
      <description> infomark console utils completion Output (bash/zsh) shell completion code
Synopsis Pipe the stdout to your completion collection, e.g.,
./infomark console utils completion zsh &amp;gt; ~/.my-shell/completions/_infomark
infomark console utils completion [shell] [flags] Options -h, --help help for completion SEE ALSO  infomark console utils - Some helper functions.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils_doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_console_utils_doc/</guid>
      <description> infomark console utils doc Generates docs for console
Synopsis Generates docs for console
infomark console utils doc [flags] Options -h, --help help for doc SEE ALSO  infomark console utils - Some helper functions.  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_serve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_serve/</guid>
      <description> infomark serve start the infomark RESTful JSON backend server with configured api
Synopsis Starts a http server and serves the configured api
infomark serve [flags] Options -h, --help help for serve SEE ALSO  infomark - A CI based course framework  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/commands/infomark_work/</guid>
      <description> infomark work start a worker
Synopsis Starts a background worker which will use docker to test submissions. Can be used with the flag &amp;ldquo;-n&amp;rdquo; to start multiple workers within one process.
infomark work [flags] Options -h, --help help for work -n, --number int number of workers within one routine (default 1) SEE ALSO  infomark - A CI based course framework  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 30-Apr-2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrator&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/administrator/</guid>
      <description>General Information This page gives a brief overview of the underlying system and capabilities. It is meant to be read by people who would like to install the system. If you are provided such an instance, please refer to the Instructor&amp;rsquo;s Guide
The InfoMark System can serve multiple courses within a single server instance. The linked background workers will then be shared amongst these courses.
Configuration The configuration is done within a YAML configuration file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/console/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/console/</guid>
      <description>InfoMark Console The backend includes a console for common tasks like doing/restoring a backup, manually confirm user accounts or set permissions.
 Currently, the console can only be accessed directly on the server. Most operations will be migrated to the CLI example implementation.
  Source InfoMark CLI
 Documentation InfoMark Server Console</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/developer/</guid>
      <description>The System is managed via two git-repositories. Both parts are tested separately using continuous integration tests. It is a good idea to read the .drone.yml configuration on how to build these parts from source.
Whenever a combination is stable, we will create a new release, which can be downloaded here:
 Download InfoMark
Frontend  
We use the Elm language to create a robust and fast implementation. Elm compiles to JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/overview/</guid>
      <description>InfoMark is a free, scalable, modern, and open-source online course management system supporting auto-testing of programming assignments scaling to thousands of students and several courses.
Uploaded solutions to programming assignments are tested automatically. For more information about writing such tests, see our Tutor&amp;rsquo;s Guide. On how to use the system, please refer to the Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Guide. And for development, please refer to our Developer&amp;rsquo;s Guide.
Teaching assistants (tutors) can grade these homework solutions online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queries</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/queries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/queries/</guid>
      <description>To run queries for the purpose of doing some statistics we highly recommend to make a snapshot of the database as illustrated in the &amp;ldquo;Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Guide&amp;rdquo;. Above is a collection of usefule SQL snippets. The app pgweb is quite useful.
Getting distribution of students to groups To gest a list of how students are distributed to groups. This is useful when manually creating/changing assignments:
SELECT count(*), ug.group_id, g.description FROM user_group ug INNER JOIN groups g ON g.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutor&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://infomark.org/guides/tutor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infomark.org/guides/tutor/</guid>
      <description>Auto - Tests Auto-tests (unit-tests) consists of
 a submission &amp;lt;STUDENT_UPLOAD.ZIP&amp;gt; made by a student a testing framework &amp;lt;TASK_SEPCIFIC_TEST.ZIP&amp;gt; written by one of the tutors/instructors a docker-image name &amp;lt;YOUR_DOCKER_IMAGE&amp;gt;  Each infomark-worker will fetch a submission from a queue and execute a command which is similar to
docker run --rm -it --net=&amp;#34;none&amp;#34; \  -v &amp;lt;STUDENT_UPLOAD.ZIP&amp;gt;:/data/submission.zip:ro \  -v &amp;lt;TASK_SEPCIFIC_TEST.ZIP&amp;gt;:/data/unittest.zip:ro \  &amp;lt;YOUR_DOCKER_IMAGE&amp;gt; The output will be stored in the database and displayed to the student resp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>